Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2010
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2010
Mus. Arc. 55
Haupt, Irene
1 DVD (134 digital images in tiff format)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Contains 134 digital images of musicians who participated in the June in Buffalo Festival 2010 at the University at Buffalo.
All files in the collection renamed to reflect chronological sequence. Renamed files stored with the collection on a separate DVD.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from Irene Haupt, 2010.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
The entire collection of images from June in Buffalo 2010 is available in the University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.
Biographical Note
Irene Haupt, a graduate of the State University of New York at Buffalo, has been documenting the Buffalo arts scene through her photography since 1976. During that time she has worked for, or with, some of the most notable institutions in Buffalo, including the Irish Classical Theatre, Studio Arena Theater, the Kavinoky Theatre, the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, the Theatre of Youth, the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, and the State University of New York at Buffalo. In addition to her specialty of theater photography, Irene Haupt has also devoted much of her career to the photography of musicians and musical events. Most notable is her documentation of the contemporary music scene in Buffalo, including coverage of the University at Buffalo's June in Buffalo festival of new music, 1982-1987, and 2000 to the present. Over the course of those years, she has created a visual record that contains images of some of the most significant composers and performers of the last quarter century. The list of names is impressive: Aaron Copland, Morton Feldman, Leo Smit, Virgil Thomson, Steve Reich, Ralph Shapey, Henry Brant, Earle Brown, Ursula Oppens, Jan Williams, Lukas Foss, Philip Glass, Otto Luening, Conlon Nancarrow, Ernst Krenek, Larry Austin, Lejaren Hiller, Elliott Carter, Milton Babbitt, John Cage, Charles Wuorinen, Jacob Druckman, and Yvar Mikhashoff, among others.
The June in Buffalo festival of contemporary music was begun at the University at Buffalo in 1975 by composer Morton Feldman. He directed the festival 1975-1978 and in 1980. The festival was dormant from 1981 through 1985. David Felder revived the festival in 1986 and has been its director since that time.
Scope and Content Note
The collection of Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2010 contains 134 digital images of participants in the festival for 2010. The list of musicians includes David Felder, Brad Lubman, Irvine Arditti, Olivier Pasquet, James Baker, Julia Bentley, Bernard Rands, JoAnn Falletta, Roger Reynolds, Augusta Read Thomas, Steve Reich, the Signal Ensemble, Ensemble SurPlus, Ensemble Laboratorium, the Arditti Quartet, the Slee Sinfonietta, and the Buffalo Philharmonic.
Arrangement
One series arranged chronologically.
Container List
- Ensemble SurPlus members Stefan Haussler, Eun-Ju Kim, Thomas Avery (acting as page-turner), and Beverley Ellis rehearsing Jordan Kuspa's Piano trio at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-30, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Surplus rehearsal KUSPA.tif (Image-file JIB2010_001)
- Ensemble SurPlus members Stefan Haussler, Eun-Ju Kim, Thomas Avery (acting as page-turner), and Beverley Ellis rehearsing Jordan Kuspa's Piano trio at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-30, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: JIB rehearsal Surplusfor KUSPA.tif (Image-file JIB2010_002)
- Ensemble SurPlus members Stefan Haussler, Eun-Ju Kim, Thomas Avery (acting as page-turner), and Beverley Ellis rehearsing Jordan Kuspa's Piano trio at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-30, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: SURPLUS rehearsal JIB.tif (Image-file JIB2010_003)
- Composer Olivier Pasquet at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Olivier Pasquet.tif (Image-file JIB2010_004)
- Composers David Felder and Olivier Pasquet with student composers at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: David Felder with students and composers.tif (Image-file JIB2010_005)
- Student composers Diana Soh, Chun Ting Pang, and Shiuan Chang at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: student composers Diana Soh, Chung Ting Pang, Shiuan Chang, .tif (Image-file JIB2010_006)
- Composer David Felder with student composers Gabriele Vanoni and Daniel Bassin at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: David Felder with student composers Daniel Bassin, Gabriele .tif (Image-file JIB2010_007)
- Composer Olivier Pasquet with student composers Diana Soh and David Hudry at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer Olivier Pasquet, Diana Soh, David Hudry.tif (Image-file JIB2010_008)
- Composer David Felder with June in Buffalo 2010 students Chun Ting Pang, Joe Lake, and Jacob Gotlib, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer David Felder with student composersChun Ting Pang,J.tif (Image-file JIB2010_009)
- James Baker conducting a rehearsal of Roger Reynolds's work, Aspiration, with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 002.tif (Image-file JIB2010_010)
- Conductor Brad Lubman rehearsing Signal Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: conductor Brad Lubman.tif (Image-file JIB2010_011)
- Brad Lubman conducting the Signal Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Brad Lubman conductor SIGNAL.tif (Image-file JIB2010_012)
- Percussionists David Skidmore and Doug Perkins during rehearsal with the Signal Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 016.tif (Image-file JIB2010_013)
- Composer Steve Reich at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Composer Steve Reich June in Buffalo 2010.tif (Image-file JIB2010_014)
- Composer Steve Reich at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer Steve Reich=.tif (Image-file JIB2010_015)
- Composer Steve Reich and conductor Brad Lubman at rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Steve Reich Brad Lubman, conductor.tif (Image-file JIB2010_016)
- Composer Francois Eckert at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Francois Eckert, composer workshop.tif (Image-file JIB2010_017)
- Composer Francois Eckert at computer during workshop at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer Francois Eckert.tif (Image-file JIB2010_018)
- Ensemble SurPlus members Martina Roth, Erich Wagner, Christian Kemper, Stefan Haussler, violin, Thomas Avery, and Adrian Romaniuc rehearsing Lukas Foss's work, Music for Six at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Ensemble SurPlus rehearsing Lukas Foss-.tif (Image-file JIB2010_019)
- Ensemble SurPlus members Martina Roth, Erich Wagner, Christian Kemper, Stefan Haussler, violin, Thomas Avery, and Adrian Romaniuc rehearsing Lukas Foss's work, Music for Six at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: ensemble SurPlus rehearsing Lukas Foss.tif (Image-file JIB2010_020)
- Student composer Ashley Wang rehearsing her work Intimate Rejection with pianist Eric Huebner at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Eric Huebner Ashley Wang Workshop Performance.tif (Image-file JIB2010_021)
- Student composer Ashley Wang rehearsing her work, Intimate Rejection with pianist Eric Huebner at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Ashley Wang Eric Huebner Workshop Performance.tif (Image-file JIB2010_022)
- Violoncellist Jonathan Golove rehearsing student composer Shiuan Chang's work, Warrior Dance at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Jonathan Golove cello student composer Shiuan Chang Workshop.tif (Image-file JIB2010_023)
- Brad Lubman conducting the Signal Ensemble in a workshop performance of student composer Peter Van Zandt Lane's work, Magana at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: SIGNAL ensemble Workshop.tif (Image-file JIB2010_024)
- Brad Lubman conducting the Signal Ensemble in a workshop performance of student composer Peter Van Zandt Lane's work, Magana at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: SIGNAL ensemble workshop=.tif (Image-file JIB2010_025)
- Conductor Brad Lubman talking with student composer Emily Koh during workshop performance of Koh's work, Circum perceptio with the Signal Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Workshop with Emily Koh student composer.tif (Image-file JIB2010_026)
- Conductor Brad Lubman talking with student composer Emily Koh during workshop at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Workshop Brad Lubman with Emily Koh.tif (Image-file JIB2010_027)
- Brad Lubman conducting the Signal Ensemble in a workshop performance of student composer Matthew Heap's work, Illicit Trysts at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Workshop Signal ensemble.tif (Image-file JIB2010_028)
- Conductor Brad Lubman with composer Matthew Heap rehearsing the Signal Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Workshop with student composer Matthew Heap.tif (Image-file JIB2010_029)
- Conductor Brad Lubman with composer Matthew Heap rehearsing the Signal Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Brad Lubman conductor with Signal ensemble and student compo.tif (Image-file JIB2010_030)
- Brad Lubman conducting members of the Signal Ensemble in workshop performance of student composer Matthew Heap's work, Illicit Trysts at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Workshop Performance of JIB Participants.tif (Image-file JIB2010_031)
- Conductor Brad Lubman addressing the audience at workshop performance by the Signal Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Workshop Performance of JIB.tif (Image-file JIB2010_032)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and members of the Signal Ensemble taking a bow after a workshop performance at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: SIGNAL Workshop Participants of JIB Brad Lubman conductor.tif (Image-file JIB2010_033)
- Conductor Brad Lubman with members of the Signal Ensemble after performance of student composer Emily Koh's work, circum perceptio at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Workshop Performance of JIB Participants SIGNAL.tif (Image-file JIB2010_034)
- Violoncellist Jonathan Golove during workshop performance of Shiuan Chang's work, Warrior Dance at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Workshop Performance Jonathan Golove Cello playing Shiuan C.tif (Image-file JIB2010_035)
- Pianist Eric Huebner performing student composer Ashley Wang's work, Intimate Rejection at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Eric Huebner piano Ashley Wang Intimate Rejection Workshop P.tif (Image-file JIB2010_036)
- Signal Ensemble performing Steve Reich's Sextet at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: SIGNAL SEXTET.tif (Image-file JIB2010_037)
- Signal Ensemble performing Steve Reich's Sextet at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Sextet Steve Reich, SIGNAL ensemble.tif (Image-file JIB2010_038)
- Signal Ensemble performing Steve Reich's Sextet at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Signal Ensemble Steve Reich SEXTET.tif (Image-file JIB2010_039)
- Signal Ensemble performing Steve Reich's Sextet at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: STEVE REICH Sextet SIGNAL ensemble.tif (Image-file JIB2010_040)
- Signal Ensemble performing Steve Reich's Sextet at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: SIGNAL ENSEMBLE.tif (Image-file JIB2010_041)
- Brad Lubman conducting the Signal Ensemble in a performance of Steve Reich's Double Sextet at June in Buffalo 2010. Players, from left to right are: Courtney Orlando, Lauren Radnofsky, Oliver Hagen, Bill Kalinkos, Keli Kathman, Doug Perkins, Jessica Schmitz, David Skidmore, Ken Thomson, Caitlin Sullivan, Caleb Burhans, and David Friend, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Signal ensemble STEVE REICH Double Sextet.tif (Image-file JIB2010_042)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and the Signal Ensemble after a performance of Steve Reich's Double Sextet at June in Buffalo 2010. Players, from left to right are: Courtney Orlando, Lauren Radnofsky, Bill Kalinkos, Oliver Hagen, Keli Kathman, Doug Perkins, Jessica Schmitz, David Skidmore, Ken Thomson, Caleb Burhans, and Caitlin Sullivan, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: SIGNAL Ensemble Brad Lubman conductor an evening with Steve .tif (Image-file JIB2010_043)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, composer Steve Reich, and the Signal Ensemble after a performance of Reich's Double Sextet at June in Buffalo 2010. Players are, left to right, Courtney Orlando, Lauren Radnofsky, Bill Kalinkos, Oliver Friend, Keli Kathman, Doug Perkins, Jessica Schmitz, David Skidmore, Ken Thomson, Caleb Burhans, and Caitlin Sullivan, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Brad Lubman with Steve Reich Signal ensemble.tif (Image-file JIB2010_044)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, composer Steve Reich, and the Signal Ensemble after a performance of Reich's Double Sextet at June in Buffalo 2010. Players, from left to right are: Courtney Orlando, Lauren Radnofsky, Bill Kalinkos, Oliver Hagen, Keli Kathman, Doug Perkins, Jessica Schmitz, David Skidmore, Caleb Burhans, Ken Thomson, and Caitlin Sullivan, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Steve Reich with Brad Lubman SIGNAL ENSEMBLE.tif (Image-file JIB2010_045)
- Composer Steve Reich and conductor Brad Lubman applaud the members of the Signal Ensemble after a performance of Reich's Double Sextet at June in Buffalo 2010. From left to right after Lubman: pianist Oliver Hagen, percussionists Doug Perkins and David Skidmore, clarinetist Bill Kalinkos, pianist David Friend, flutists Jessica Schmitz and Keli Kathman, violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky, violinist Courtney Orlando, clarinetist Ken Thomson, violinist Caleb Burhans, and violoncellist Caitlin Sullivan, 2010-05-31, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 124.tif (Image-file JIB2010_046)
- Sven Thomas Kiebler conducting Thomas Avery and other members of Ensemble SurPlus in rehearsal of Morton Feldman's Viola in My Life II at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: SurPlus rehearsal for Viola in my Life II by Morton Feldman.tif (Image-file JIB2010_047)
- Composers David Felder and Steve Reich presenting a lecture at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Lecture David Felder Steve -Reich--.tif (Image-file JIB2010_048)
- Composers David Felder and Steve Reich presenting a lecture at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Lecture David Felder Steve Reich--.tif (Image-file JIB2010_049)
- Composers David Felder and Steve Reich presenting a lecture at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Lecture Steve Reich and David Felder composer.tif (Image-file JIB2010_050)
- University at Buffalo president John B. Simpson with composers Steve Reich and David Felder at ceremony presenting Steve Reich with the SUNY Honorary Doctorate in Music in 2010, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: President John B. Simpson Steve Reich David Felder.tif (Image-file JIB2010_051)
- University at Buffalo president John B. Simpson and SUNY trustee Eunice Lewin placing the SUNY Honorary Doctorate in Music hood upon composer Steve Reich, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: President John B. Simpson Steve Reich Mrs. Eunice Lewin(Sun.tif (Image-file JIB2010_052)
- University at Buffalo president John B. Simpson and SUNY trustee Eunice Lewin placing the SUNY Honorary Doctorate in Music hood upon composer Steve Reich, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: President John B. Simpson Steve Reich Mrs.Eunice Lewin ( SUN.tif (Image-file JIB2010_053)
- University at Buffalo president John B. Simpson, along with SUNY trustee Eunice Lewin, conferring SUNY Honorary Doctorate in Music to composer Steve Reich, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: SUNY Honorary Degree Conferral and Presentation composer Dr..tif (Image-file JIB2010_054)
- Thomas Avery performing as solo violist in Morton Feldman's Viola in My Life II at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: THOMAS Avery, viola plays Morton Feldman Viola in my life I.tif (Image-file JIB2010_055)
- Ensemble SurPlus members Sven Thomas Kiebler, Martina Roth, Erich Wagner, and Adrian Romaniuc performing Brian Ferneyhough's work, Mort Subite at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: --Ensemble SurPlus.tif (Image-file JIB2010_056)
- Ensemble SurPlus members Thomas Avery, Sven Thomas Kiebler, and Beverley Ellis performing Alvin Lucier's Fideliotrio at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Alvin Lucier Fideliotrio Ensemble Surplus.tif (Image-file JIB2010_057)
- Sven Thomas Kiebler conducting Ensemble SurPlus members violinist Stefan Haussler, double bassist Johannes Nied, and percussionist Adrian Romaniuc in a performance of Charles Wuorinen's Spinoff at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: -Ensemble Surplus.tif (Image-file JIB2010_058)
- Sven Thomas Kiebler conducting violinist Stefan Haussler, double bassist Johannes Nied, and percussionist Adrian Romaniuc in a performance of Charles Wuorinen's Spinoff at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Charles Wuorinen Spinoff Violin (1983) Sven Thomas Kiebler, .tif (Image-file JIB2010_059)
- Sven Thomas Kiebler conducting violinist Stefan Haussler, double bassist Johannes Nied, and percussionist Adrian Romaniuc in a performance of Charles Wuorinen's Spinoff at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Spinoff Violin by Charles Wuorinen Sven Thomas Kiebler,condu.tif (Image-file JIB2010_060)
- Ensemble SurPlus members Sven Thomas Kiebler and Christian Kemper performing Brian Ferneyhough's work, Coloratura at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Ensemble SurPlusin Coloratura (1966) by Brian Ferneyhough.tif (Image-file JIB2010_061)
- Pianist Sven Thomas Kiebler and oboist Christian Kemper after a performance of Brian Ferneyhough's Coloratura, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Coloratura (1966) by Brian Ferneyhough Ensemble SurPlus.tif (Image-file JIB2010_062)
- Ensemble SurPlus on stage after a performance at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-01, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Black Box Theater Ensemble SurPlus Center for the Arts.tif (Image-file JIB2010_063)
- Ensemble SurPlus on stage after a performance at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: SurPlus Ensemble Center for the Arts Black Box Theater.tif (Image-file JIB2010_064)
- Conductor Baldur Bronnimann with student composer Diana Soh at rehearsal of Soh's work, Cross-Sightedness at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: conductor Baldur Broennimann, student composer Diana Soh at .tif (Image-file JIB2010_065)
- Student composers John Bacon and Gabriele Vanoni at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: student composrs John Bacon,Gabriele Vanoni at Laboratorium.tif (Image-file JIB2010_066)
- Ensemble SurPlus onstage at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: SurPlus Ensemble===.tif (Image-file JIB2010_067)
- James Baker conducting the Slee Sinfonietta and violinist Irvine Arditti in a rehearsal of Roger Reynolds's work, Aspiration at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 080.tif (Image-file JIB2010_068)
- James Baker conducting the Slee Sinfonietta and violinist Irvine Arditti in a rehearsal of Roger Reynolds's work, Aspiration at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Rehearsal for David Felder Tweener Slee Sinfonietta June in .tif (Image-file JIB2010_069)
- Percussionist Jonathan Hepfer performing with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: June in Buffalo 2010 086.tif (Image-file JIB2010_070)
- Percussionist Jonathan Hepfer rehearsing with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Percussion.tif (Image-file JIB2010_071)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti rehearsing Roger Reynolds's work, Aspiration at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: Violinist soloist Irvine Arditti rehearsing Roger Reynolds A.tif (Image-file JIB2010_072)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti rehearsing Roger Reynolds's work, Aspiration at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: violinist soloist Irvine Arditte at June in Buffalo rehearsi.tif (Image-file JIB2010_073)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti rehearsing Roger Reynolds's work, Aspiration at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: violinist soloist Irvin Arditti rehearsing Roger Reynolds As.tif (Image-file JIB2010_074)
- Composer Roger Reynolds conferring with conductor James Baker at rehearsal of Reynolds's work, Aspiration, with the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer Roger Reynolds looking at his score with conductor .tif (Image-file JIB2010_075)
- Composer Roger Reynolds looking at the score of his work, Aspiration, at rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2010, 2010-06-02, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original filename: composer Roger Reynolds.tif (Image-file JIB2010_076)